[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Nothing says "First day of the new quarter"
- 没有什么比一张崭新的塑封课程表更能代表新季度的开始了。
like a freshly-laminated schedule.
- 有手在，谁还需要塑封机？
- Who needs laminating when you got a hand?
这学期，我有...谜团。
This period, I have... mystery.
- 你是说“历史”吧。
- You mean "History." - No.
- 不。
I have no idea what this says.
我完全不知道这上面写的是什么。
- Well, the three of us have art class.
- 好吧，我们三个人都有美术课。
Finally, a reason to wear this beret.
终于有个理由戴这顶贝雷帽了。
- Plus, art's an easy A.
- 而且，美术课很容易得A。
But then, for me, aren't they all?
但对我来说，不都是这样吗？
- Wow, new quarter, same old Ricky,
哇，新学期，还是老样子的Ricky，
already bragging about his grades.
已经开始炫耀他的成绩了。
- If it's true, it's not bragging.
如果这是真的，那不算炫耀。
It's just talking.
只是说话而已。
- Well, it sounds to me like trash talking.
对我来说，听起来就像是在说大话。
- No, this is trash talking:
不，这才是说大话：
I'm gonna get a better grade than you in art class
我会在美术课上拿到比你更好的成绩
and then, I'm gonna brag about it.
然后，我会炫耀一番。
- Hey, are you guys coming to the Student Events Club after school?
嘿，你们放学后会去学生活动俱乐部吗？
We really need some ideas for the spring festival.
我们真的需要一些春季庆典的点子。
- Definitely. - I'll bring chips.
- 当然。 - 我会带薯片。
- I can bring some dip.
- 我可以带一些蘸酱。
- Why am I just now hearing about this club?
- 为什么我现在才听说这个俱乐部？
Where do I sign up?
我在哪里报名？
- Dicky, that club's all about
- 迪基，那个俱乐部全是关于
organizing events and coming up with ideas.
组织活动和想点子的。
- Uh, yeah, with chips and girls.
- 呃，是的，还有薯片和女生。
[bell rings]
[铃声响起]
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- You know, Ricky, I am pretty good at art.
你知道，Ricky，我在艺术方面相当不错。
I wouldn't be so sure you're going to be better at it than me.
我可不认为你会比我更擅长。
- Please, I've been coloring inside the lines
拜托，我从三岁起就能在线内涂色了。
since I was three.
我很确定我能搞定这个。
Pretty sure I got this.
毕加索曾经说过，
- Pablo Picasso once said that
“艺术是一种谎言...”
"Art is a lie...
“...却道出了真相。”
that tells the truth."
那到底是什么意思？
- What does that even mean? - Exactly!
正是如此！
I believe we all
我相信我们每个人
have an artist who lives inside of us,
我们每个人心中都有一个艺术家，
screaming to get out.
渴望着被释放。
[screams]
[尖叫]
So today, I want you
所以今天，我希望你们
to create a piece that expresses you.
创作一件能表达你自己的作品。
Your-- your hopes,
你的——你的希望，
your dreams,
你的梦想，
your truth.
你的真实。
- Oh, can I paint a self-portrait?
- 哦，我可以画自画像吗？
- Any subject.
- 任何主题。
- Ooh, uh, can I make something out of food?
- 噢，我能用食物做点什么吗？
- Any medium. - [gasps] Sweet!
- 任何材料都可以。- [倒吸气]太好了！
Or salty. Haven't decided yet.
或者咸的。还没决定。
- Um, what about a paper?
- 那，用纸怎么样？
- Yes, you can use paper.
- 当然，你可以用纸。
- Uh, no. Can I write a paper?
- 呃，不是。我能写篇文章吗？
- Oh. [laughs]
- 哦。[笑]
This assignment isn't about
这次作业不是要写文章吧？
writing papers, right?
而是要展现我们的创造力。
It's about expressing our creativity.
- 那么，有什么指导原则吗？- 没有指导原则。
- So, what are the guidelines? - There are no guidelines.
- 那么，有什么指导方针吗？ - 没有指导方针。
- Then can I write a paper?
- 那我可以写一篇论文吗？
- There is one guideline. No papers.
- 有一个指导方针。不可以写论文。
- So, what should I make? - Anything you like.
- 那我应该做什么？ - 任何你喜欢的东西。
Just express yourself!
只要表达你自己！
- Well, I'd like to express
- 嗯，我想表达的是
how much I'd like some guidelines.
我有多么希望有一些指导方针。
How else will I know how to get an A?
否则我怎么知道如何得到A呢？
- Oh, we don't have grades in here.
- 哦，我们这里不评分。
[both gasp]
[两人同时惊讶]
All right, class.
好吧，同学们。
On your marks...
各就各位...
get set...
准备...
create!
创作吧！
- [breathing heavily]
- [呼吸沉重]
- I hear something.
- 我听到什么声音。
Oh.
哦。
I think it's the little artist
我想这是你内心的小艺术家在哭泣。
inside of you crying.
[轻快的音乐]
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ One, two ♪ ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Mae, would you like to read back
- Mae，你想读一下上次会议的纪要吗？
the minutes from last meeting?
- 是的。
- Yes.
你问是否有人对春季节日有想法，
You asked if anyone had ideas for the spring festival,
我们都说了“没有”，
we all said "Nope,"
然后Natlee的椅子发出了吱吱声。
then Natlee's "chair squeaked."
然后我们迅速散会了。
Then we quickly adjourned.
- 嘿，这是“学生活动俱乐部”吗？
- Hey, is this "Student Events Club?"
- 你在这里做什么？
- What are you doing here?
- 我只是觉得这个俱乐部需要一些男性意见。女士们。
- I just thought this club could use some dude input.
我只是觉得这个俱乐部需要一些男生的意见。
Ladies.
女士们。
- You know what? I don't have time to fight this.
你知道吗？我没时间争论这个。
Okay, we have three days until the spring festival,
好吧，我们还有三天时间直到春季音乐节，
and we need to raise money for our class trip,
我们需要为班级旅行筹集资金，
so let's think of some ideas.
所以让我们想一些主意。
- How about a dance-a-thon? - We did that last year.
舞蹈马拉松怎么样？我们在去年做过了。
- Walk-a-thon? - Eighth grade is doing that.
步行马拉松？八年级在做那个。
- Skip-a-thon? - That's not a thing.
跳绳马拉松？那不是个事。
- Then I got noth-on.
那我没什么主意了。
- Come on, guys. We need to think.
来吧，伙计们。我们需要动动脑筋。
- Forget thinking.
别想了。
Just say the first thing that pops into your head.
直接说出你脑子里第一个冒出来的想法。
I'll start.
我先来。
Me in a kissing booth.
我在一个接吻亭里。
Boom.
砰。
Why don't we grab a smoothie and hammer out the details?
要不我们去喝杯 smoothie，然后敲定细节？
- Dicky, we're trying to work.
Dicky，我们正在努力工作。
- So am I.
我也是。
- Look, this club is for people
听着，这个俱乐部是为那些
who are serious about helping the school.
那些真正致力于帮助学校的人。
- Yeah, if you're not gonna help,
- 是的，如果你不打算帮忙，
you can just go sit in the back.
你可以直接去后面坐着。
- No, I'm gonna help.
- 不，我会帮忙的。
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
[chair squeaks] It was the chair.
[椅子吱吱响] 是椅子的问题。
- See?
- 看吧？
- Meeting adjourned!
- 会议结束！
[mouthing words]
[无声说话]
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- Hey. - Ooh, uh, Mom?
- 嘿。 - 哦，呃，妈妈？
Can I get your opinion on these?
我能听听你对这些的看法吗？
- Oh, sure.
- 哦，当然。
Aww. [chuckles]
哎呀。[轻笑]
Mmm.
嗯。
Delicious.
美味。
- What are you doing?
- 你在做什么？
- What? You wanted my opinion!
- 什么？你不是要我给意见吗！
- This is my art project,
- 这是我的艺术项目，
not an all-you-can-eat panda buffet.
不是自助熊猫大餐。
- Sorry.
- 对不起。
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
- So are you gonna fix that little guy-- - Just finish it. - Thank you.
- 所以你要修好那个小家伙吗？- 只要完成它。- 谢谢。
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Ready... set...
- 准备... 开始...
create!
创作！
Create!
Ah! - Whoa.
啊！- 哇。
If you're going for mayonnaise in a snow storm,
如果你想在暴风雪中制作蛋黄酱，
then you got it.
那你就能做到。
- I got nothing!
- 我什么都没有！
I'm trying, but without guidelines,
我正在尝试，但没有指导方针，
I don't know where to start.
我不知道从哪里开始。
- It's easy. Just do this.
- 这很简单。就这样做。
You've got a sky here...
你这里有一片天空...
um... a little cottage there...
嗯...那边有一个小屋...
some grass...
一些草地...
a little tree-- oh!
一棵小树——哦！
And how about a puppy?
那来只小狗怎么样？
- I don't see any of those things,
- 我没看到那些东西，
but it's amazing! - Yeah, it's pretty good.
但真是太神奇了！ - 是啊，相当不错。
- I can't believe I'm saying this,
- 我简直不敢相信我会这么说，
but tell me your thought process.
但告诉我你的思考过程。
- Okay, well, step one, I grab a brush.
- 好的，首先，第一步，我拿起画笔。
Step two, I put some paint on it.
第二步，我在上面涂些颜料。
Step three, I painted.
第三步，我开始画画。
Step four, you asked me how I did it.
第四步，你问我怎么做到的。
Step five, I told you.
第五步，我告诉了你。
Step six, I go eat a burrito.
第六步，我去吃个墨西哥卷饼。
- Wait, I can't even get to step three.
等等，我连第三步都到不了。
This is due tomorrow, and I have nothing.
这个明天就要交了，我什么都没做。
- Just hand in mine.
直接交我的吧。
- I can't take credit for something I didn't do.
我不能为没做过的事情邀功。
- Oh. I respect that.
哦，我尊重这一点。
I don't get it, but I respect it.
我不太明白，但我尊重。
- Okay. Step one, pick up the brush.
好吧。第一步，拿起画笔。
[deep breath] Step two, put some paint on it.
[深呼吸] 第二步，蘸点颜料。
Step three...
第三步...
- Step three looks hard. - [gasps]
- 第三步看起来很难。 - [吸气]
- Hey, you know what my painting has
- 嘿，你知道我的画有什么
that yours doesn't?
而你的没有吗？
Paint.
颜料。
Step four, laugh my way up the stairs.
第四步，笑着上楼梯。
[laughs]
[笑]
- We'll see who has the last step four.
- 我们看看谁最后能完成第四步。
Ricky...
瑞奇...
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- Your truth has moved me.
- 你的真实感动了我。
I mean, the honesty, the bravery,
我的意思是，这份诚实，这份勇气，
in this hand turkey...
在这个手火鸡里...
I-- I'm sorry, I can't!
我... 对不起，我做不到！
- Uh, Ms. Gressle?
- 呃，格雷斯尔女士？
Where's my project?
我的项目在哪里？
Uh, it was the panda rice balls.
呃，是熊猫饭团。
- I'm sorry. I didn't get them.
- 对不起，我没拿到。
- What? I left them on your desk this morning.
- 什么？我早上把它们放在你桌子上了。
- That's strange. but since it was food,
- 这很奇怪。但既然是食物，
it might have been taken away by rats.
它可能已经被老鼠拿走了。
- Rats! - Or the janitor.
- 老鼠！ - 或者是清洁工。
- Mr. Katz!
- 卡茨先生！
- I'll give you another day to redo it.
- 我再给你一天时间重做。
- Redo it!
- 重做！
- Ah, Dawn.
- 啊，道恩。
Your painting is simply...
你的画真是...
mm, mm, mm!
嗯，嗯，嗯！
- Did you hear that, Ricky? My painting is...
- 你听到了吗，里奇？我的画是...
"Mm, mm, mm!"
嗯，嗯，嗯！
- Oh, and look at this one. [gasps]
哦，再看看这个。[吸气声]
- Oh, that's mine.
哦，这是我的。
How does it sound, Ms. Gressle?
听起来怎么样，格雷斯尔女士？
- Ahhhhh!
啊！
- Hear that? Mine's, "Ahhhhh!"
听到了吗？我的画是，“啊！”
- Um, excuse me, Ms. Gressle, "Mm--mm--mm!"
嗯，对不起，格雷斯尔女士，“嗯——嗯——嗯！”
Is better than, "Ahhhhh!" Right?
比“啊！”更好，对吧？
- Dawn, I could never say that one piece
道恩，我永远不会说某一幅画比另一幅更好，但在这种情况下，
is better than another, but in this case,
one is better.
一个更好。
In fact, I'm going to hang one of these paintings
事实上，我现在就要把其中一幅画挂在大厅里。
up in the hall right now.
挂在大厅里。
Dawn?
黎明？
- Yes, Ms. Gressle?
- 是的，格雷斯尔女士？
- You're tall, come help me hang Ricky's painting
- 你个子高，来帮我挂里基的画在大厅里。- 我不认为——
up in the hall. - I don't think--
- 你知道我的画有什么你的画没有的吗？
- You know what my painting has that yours doesn't?
你挂它！
You hanging it!
- 里基！
- Ricky!
[rock music]
♪ ♪
看！
- Behold!
掌声
[applause]
我相信是格雷斯尔女士曾经说过
- I believe it was Ms. Gressle who once said
是毕加索曾经说过，
it was Picasso who once said,
“艺术是谎言...
"Art is a lie...
“艺术是谎言... 却道出了真相。”
that tells the truth."
掌声
[applause]
说到“艺术”和“谎言”，这说不通。
- Speaking of "art" and "lies," this doesn't add up.
我可不买账。
I'm not buying it. - It's not for sale.
我不信。 - 这幅画不卖。
- We'll see about that.
- 咱们走着瞧。
- This painting is so cool.
- 这幅画真酷。
- I didn't know Ricky could paint.
- 我之前都不知道Ricky会画画。
- He's so talented!
- 他真有才华！
- I like a talented guy.
- 我喜欢有才华的人。
- Oh, really?
- 哦，真的吗？
Well, what would you ladies say
好吧，如果我告诉你们那幅画是我画的，
if I told you I painted that?
你们会怎么想？
[laughter] - Yeah, right, Dicky.
[笑声] - 是啊，没错，Dicky。
- What, you think I couldn't paint that?
- 什么，你认为我画不了那幅画？
- No, I know you couldn't paint that.
- 不，我知道你画不了那幅画。
- Yeah, you're "kissing booth" guy.
- 是啊，你是那个“接吻亭”的家伙。
- You never take anything seriously.
- 你从不认真对待任何事情。
- I take things seriously.
- 我认真对待事情。
- Oh, thanks for the painting, bro.
- 哦，谢谢你的画，兄弟。
- Yeah. I need it back.
- 是啊。我需要它回来。
- What? - Dude.
- 什么？ - 伙计。
The girls love my painting.
女孩们喜欢我的画。
You gotta tell them that I painted it.
你得告诉她们那是我画的。
- No, I can't do that.
不行，我不能那么做。
Then Ms. Gressle will know I lied.
否则格雷斯勒小姐会知道我说谎了。
Besides, you said I could have it.
而且，你说过可以给我的。
- But that's before I found out
但那是在我发现
people don't take me seriously.
人们不把我当回事之前。
- I'm sorry, but the painting's got my name on it.
抱歉，画上有我的名字。
- So you got my picture hanging, and now
所以你挂着我的画，现在
you're gonna leave me hanging?
却要让我失望吗？
- I'm not the bad guy here, right?
我不是坏人吧？
I mean, he told me to take it.
我是说，他让我拿走的。
- Give Dicky's painting back.
把迪基的画还给他。
- Now he's in my head!
现在他跑到我脑子里来了！
- And you should give Dicky money.
你应该给迪基钱。
- What? - Money for Dicky.
什么？
- Dicky. - Whoa.
给迪基的钱。
Did you hear that too?
哇哦。
[rock music]
你也有听到吗？
- I'm sorry, I just can't
对不起，我只是不能告诉别人那幅画是你的。
tell people the painting's yours.
好吧，那我就再画一幅
- Fine, then I'll paint
不行，那样大家都会知道我在撒谎。
another painting just like it.
我会再画一幅一模一样的。
- No, then everyone will know I lied.
不行，那样大家都会知道我说谎了。
Besides, you only want it back
而且，你只是想拿回来
so you can impress some "girls."
去给某些“女孩”留下印象。
- This isn't just about girls.
这不仅仅是为了女孩。
This is about letting people know
这是为了让人们知道
that I do take some things seriously
我确实对某些事情很认真
and if those people just happen to be girls,
如果那些人恰好是女孩，
then so be it.
那也就这样吧。
- I can't give you the painting back,
我不能把画还给你，
but I also can't leave you hanging.
但我也不能让你悬而未决。
So, maybe there is something I can do
所以，或许我可以做些什么
to help you be taken seriously.
来帮助你被认真对待。
- I'm listening. - Okay.
我在听。
You made me look like a good artist,
你让我看起来像个好艺术家，
so I'm gonna make you look like a good idea man.
所以我要让你看起来像个好点子王。
What we're gonna do is-- - Okay--
我们要做的是——
Oh--[forced chuckle] - Um--
哦——[勉强笑出声]
How 'bout that televised sporting event
你和我都看过的那场电视直播的体育赛事怎么样？
that you and I both watched?
是的。体育。
- Yes. Sports.
是的，体育。
- What do you say we go upstairs
我们上楼继续讨论这个体育赛事怎么样？
and keep discussing this sporting event?
是的，体育，上楼。
- Yes. Sports. Upstairs.
伙计，那场地真大。
- Man, that was a big field. - And grassy.
而且绿草如茵。
- [sighs] Something's up with Ricky and Dicky.
（叹气）Ricky和Dicky有点不对劲。
I'm gonna figure out what it is.
我会弄清楚是怎么回事。
- I don't have time for that.
我没时间管那个。
I'm redoing my art project.
我正在重新做我的艺术项目。
Making something both rats and Mr. Katz
制作一些连老鼠和Katz先生都不想碰的东西。
won't want to mess with.
不会有人想破坏它。
Octo-pie.
章鱼派。
- Just doesn't make any sense. - It makes perfect sense.
- 完全不合逻辑。- 完美合乎逻辑。
It's a pie shaped like an octopus.
它是一个章鱼形状的派。
- No. First Ricky can't paint,
- 不对。先是Ricky不会画画，
and somehow he creates the most amazing painting
然后他却创作出了学校历史上最惊人的画作
in the history of school paintings
现在他和Dicky谈论起体育来了。
and now he's talking about sports with Dicky.
他们俩对体育一窍不通。
Those two know nothing about sports.
我得查清楚这是怎么回事。
I'm gonna get to the bottom of this.
嘿，我的吸盘都去哪儿了？
- Hey, where'd all my suction cups go?
- 嘿，我的吸盘都去哪儿了？
[sighs]
[叹气]
- I think they're over there.
- 我想它们在那边。
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
Okay, so I came up with a name for our spring festival.
好吧，我为我们的春季庆典想了一个名字。
"Spring Fun For All."
“春日乐趣，人人共享。”
What do you guys think?
你们觉得怎么样？
Aww, I wasn't expecting applause.
哎呀，我没期待掌声。
Thank you. Okay.
谢谢。好吧。
So I also think we should get the orchestra
所以我还认为我们应该让管弦乐队
and drama club to perform.
和戏剧俱乐部来表演。
- Or...
- 或者...
- Dicky?
- 迪基？
- You want to make some serious money
- 你想在这个筹款活动中赚大钱吗？
at this fundraiser?
我们打算设立嘉年华摊位
We're gonna set up carnival booths
有游戏和奖品。
with games and prizes.
- 等等。这里发生了什么？
- W--wait. What's going on here?
- 梅，你做的手链很棒。
- Mae, you make great bracelets.
那么你觉得制作手链作为奖品怎么样？
So how do you feel about making bracelets as prizes?
- 这实际上很有道理。
- That actually makes sense.
- 这其实挺有道理的。
- Molly, Natlee, you guys
- 莫莉，纳特莉，你们俩
are always taking pictures of stuff.
总是拍东西。
How do you feel about running a photo booth?
你们觉得经营一个照相亭怎么样？
- That's a great idea.
- 那是个好主意。
- Wait, what's going on here?
- 等等，这里发生了什么？
- Sorry, Dawn.
- 对不起，道恩。
I mean, your ideas are good,
我是说，你的主意不错，
but Dicky's are better.
但迪基的主意更好。
- But you guys still like
- 但你们还是喜欢
my "Spring Fun For All" name, right?
我的“Spring Fun For All”名字，对吧？
- We like it. - Yeah.
- 我们喜欢它。 - 是的。
- Or, we could call it
- 或者，我们可以称之为
the "Spring Cha-Ching."
“Spring Cha-Ching”。
- Sorry, but Dicky's on fire.
- 抱歉，但Dicky现在很火。
- Okay, Spring Cha-Ching is now a thing.
- 好的，Spring Cha-Ching现在是一个东西了。
Meeting adjourned.
会议结束。
Seriously.
说真的。
- Okay, I'm confused.
- 好的，我有点困惑。
That guy with those good ideas was Dicky, right?
那个有好主意的人是Dicky，对吧？
- I want to say yes,
我想说是，
but I can't be sure.
但我不能确定。
- But Dicky doesn't even own a suit,
但Dicky甚至没有一套西装，
but Ricky does.
但Ricky有。
And Dicky doesn't have any ideas,
而且Dicky没有任何想法，
but Ricky does.
但Ricky有。
This whole thing just keeps getting weirder and weirder.
这一切变得越来越奇怪了。
- I agree.
我同意。
Yesterday, Dicky tried to take credit
昨天，Dicky试图为Ricky的画邀功。
for Ricky's painting.
但万一那画真是Dicky画的呢？
- But what if Dicky did paint that?
但如果那幅画真的是迪基画的呢？
Pretty tricky, Ricky.
真狡猾，瑞奇。
Pretty, pretty tricky.
非常，非常狡猾。
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- What you doing, Nicky?
你在做什么，尼基？
- Putting the finishing touches
在做我艺术项目的最后润色。
on my art project for the third time.
已经是第三次了。
This one's a brown rice teddy bear
这个是用糙米做的泰迪熊，
using an omelet for a blanket.
用煎蛋卷当毯子。
I call it...
我叫它……
"Go to Beddy, Teddy."
"去睡觉吧，泰迪。"
- How adorable!
- 多么可爱啊！
- Mm, it is adorable.
- 嗯，确实很可爱。
But I wish I didn't have to spend my Saturday redoing it.
但我希望不用在周六重做它。
- Well does Ms. Gressle not like your projects?
- 那么格雷斯老师不喜欢你的作品吗？
- They keep on disappearing
- 它们总是在她看到之前就消失了。
before she even gets to see them.
- 真的？那太奇怪了。
- Really? That's so weird.
嗯，我相信当她看到这个，
Well, I'm sure when she sees this one,
她一定会喜欢的。
she is gonna love it.
- 不仅创意十足，而且看起来美味到可以吃。
Not only is it creative, but it looks good enough to eat.
不仅创意十足，而且看起来美味到可以吃。
- Good enough to eat, huh?
- 美味到可以吃，是吗？
[gasps] Of course.
[惊讶] 当然。
Someone's been eating them.
有人一直在吃它们。
Who would stoop so low as to take
谁会这么卑鄙，
a child's art project and eat it?
竟然拿孩子的艺术作品来吃？
- Hmm?
- 嗯？
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
together: Say "Spring Cha-Ching!"
一起说：“春日叮当！”
all: Spring Cha-Ching!
全体：春日叮当！
- Oh, hey Nicky, did you ever find out what was happening to your art projects?
- 哦，嘿，Nicky，你有没有弄清楚你的艺术作品发生了什么事？
- I'm about to. I put purple food coloring
- 我正要查清楚。我在最新的作品里加了紫色食用色素，
in my latest one, so when someone eats it,
这样当有人吃掉它时，
I can identify the purple-trator.
我就能找出那个紫色叛徒。
- You're a weird little dude.
- 你真是个奇怪的小家伙。
- Look at us. We pulled it off.
- 看看我们。我们成功了。
The idea man and the artist.
创意人和艺术家。
- I gotta say, everything turned out perfectly.
- 我得说，一切都进行得非常完美。
- Oh, look.
- 哦，看。
It's the artist and his brilliant painting.
这是一位艺术家和他的杰作。
- Dawn just had an idea that I thought was mwah!
- 道恩刚刚有个想法，我觉得真是太棒了！
- Ricky, you're going to paint in front of everybody.
- 里基，你将在大家面前作画。
- And then, we're going to auction off the painting.
- 然后，我们将拍卖这幅画。
- Yeah, now we can all watch you paint.
- 是的，现在我们都可以看着你画画了。
Unless there's a reason that you can't paint
除非你有理由不能画画
that you would like to tell Ms. Gressle.
你想告诉格雷斯尔小姐。
- [nervous laughter]
- [紧张的笑声]
Uh, no.
呃，没有。
I-- I'm good. - Oh, good.
我——我很好。 - 哦，太好了。
Oh, you gather everyone around,
哦，你把大家都召集过来，
and I'll be right back.
我马上就回来。
- What am I gonna do? - Hold on.
- 我该怎么办？- 稍等。
The idea man has another idea.
点子大王又想到办法了。
- I'm the idea man! - Good, then what do you got?
- 我就是点子大王！- 太好了，那你有什么主意？
- I gotta paint in front of everybody! - You can't paint! - I know!
- 我得当着大家的面画画！- 你不会画画！- 我知道！
- Then that's not a very good idea!
- 那可不是个好主意！
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
- Attention, Spring Cha-Chingers!
各位春季赚钱合唱团的成员们！
Or shall I call you "Fun-For-Allers"?
还是应该叫你们'全民娱乐者'呢？
Fine. Spring Cha-Ching it is.
好吧，那就叫春钱吧。
Gather round to watch Ricky Harper
大家围过来，看里奇·哈珀
paint yet another masterpiece
再次在我们眼前
right before our very eyes.
绘制另一幅杰作。
[applause]
掌声
- Okay, listen. You got this.
好的，听着，你能做到的。
Remember the steps.
记住步骤。
One, pick up the paintbrush.
第一步，拿起画笔。
- [deep breath] - Two--
深呼吸
What was two again?
第二步是什么来着？
- They were your steps.
- 这是你的步骤。
- All I know is,
- 我只知道，
it ends with this.
最后一步是这个。
- You're no help at all.
- 你一点忙都帮不上。
Sure, I can put the brush in the paint,
当然，我可以把刷子浸在颜料里，
and smear it on the canvass,
然后在画布上涂抹，
but I have no idea what I'm--
但我完全不知道自己在做什么——
hey, I'm doing it, I'm painting!
嘿，我在画，我在画画！
I'm painting!
我在画画！
- Wait, he's actually painting.
- 等等，他真的在画画。
- Ricky's painting!
- 瑞奇在画画！
- Whose idea was this?
- 这是谁的主意？
- Probably Dicky's. He's an idea man.
- 可能是迪基的。他是个点子王。
- Well, what would you say if I told you
- 那如果我告诉你
I was the idea man.
我才是那个出主意的人呢？
- Can't you just be happy being tall?
- 你就不能仅仅因为个子高而高兴吗？
- Almost finished.
- 快完成了。
Just a little swirl here...
这里再画个小漩涡...
and another one here.
还有这里再来一个。
- I know you like 'em warm, so I'm pit-firing it up.
- 我知道你喜欢热乎的，所以我正在用坑烧法加热它。
- And...
- 然后...
voila!
瞧！
[all groan]
[大家叹气]
- Is it that bad?
- 有那么糟糕吗？
- No. No, it's good.
- 不，不糟糕，挺好的。
Shall we start the bidding at a nickel?
我们出价从五分钱开始怎么样？
- I have a confession.
- 我有个坦白。
I can't paint.
我不会画画。
- [snorts] Well, duh.
- [嗤笑] 嗯，显然。
- Dicky's the one who did the painting
- 迪基才是画走廊的那个人，不是我。
in the hallway, not me.
在走廊里的那幅画是Dicky画的，不是我。
[all gasp]
（大家都惊讶地吸了口气）
- Wow, Dicky.
哇，Dicky。
We really underestimated you.
我们真的低估你了。
- Thanks, but to be fair,
谢谢，但公平地说，
Ricky's the one who came up with all those great ideas
Ricky才是那些关于春日Cha-Ching的好点子的创造者。
for the Spring Cha-Ching.
所以，为了澄清，
- So, just to clarify,
我的两个兄弟都撒了谎，
both of my brothers lied,
而我才是对的
and I was right
这并不是自夸。这只是陈述事实。
and that's not bragging.
这不是自夸。
It's just talking.
只是陈述事实。
- Ricky! You're a liar?
- Ricky! 你是个骗子吗？
I mean, you should have just painted
我的意思是，你本可以直接画
a pair of pants on fire.
一条着火的裤子。
[gasps] - Awkward.
[惊呼] - 尴尬了。
- Looks like somebody's getting an earful.
- 看来有人要被训斥了。
[mouthing words]
[默念]
- Looks like someone's got a mouthful.
- 看来有人要被训斥了。
Of purple!
紫色的！
Ms. Gressle! Your mouth is purple!
格雷斯尔女士！你的嘴是紫色的！
You ate Beddy Teddy.
你吃了贝迪泰迪。
- Nicky! I-- I--
尼基！我——我——
I would never betray the trust of another artist.
我绝不会背叛另一位艺术家的信任。
I create art. I don't eat it.
我创作艺术。我不吃它。
That's a smudge of purple paint.
那是一抹紫色的颜料。
- Were you painting with your tongue?
你是在用舌头画画吗？
- All right, fine.
好吧，好吧。
I was eating your
我是在吃你的
magnificent art...work.
杰出的艺术品……
I just-- I was trying to cut down on carbs,
我只是——我正在尝试减少碳水化合物的摄入，
and it's so hard.
这太难了。
And I--
而且我——
I apologize, Nicky.
我道歉，Nicky。
- Listen, I'm glad you appreciate my work,
- 听着，我很高兴你欣赏我的作品，
but I had to remake it twice.
但我不得不重做了两次。
- Each time more delicious than the last.
- 每次都比上一次更美味。
I'm sorry, Nicky.
对不起，Nicky。
I'll give you an A. - Ah.
我会给你一个A。 - 啊。
- How come he gets a grade? - You want a grade?
- 他为什么能得到评分？ - 你也想要评分吗？
- I'm good.
我没事。
- Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
Sorry I outed you both in front of the whole school.
抱歉我在全校面前揭穿了你们俩。
- Well, we did lie, so we kind of deserved it.
嗯，我们确实撒了谎，所以某种程度上是自作自受。
- This couldn't have turned out worse.
这不可能变得更糟了。
- No, but I have an idea that could make it better.
不，但我有个主意可以让情况好转。
Everybody smile!
大家笑一个！
- This was a great idea, Dicky.
这是个好主意，迪基。
- What? It was my idea. - Huh?
什么？那是我的主意。
- No, taking the photo was your idea.
不，拍照是你的主意。
The photo booth was my idea.
这个照相亭是我的主意。
- That I gave you! - Not it's not!
- 那是我给你的！ - 不是的！
[overlapping shouting]
[重叠的喊叫声]
- Don't wear that, you don't have the right to wear--
- 别穿那个，你没有权利穿--
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪